<?xml version="1.0"?>
<DictionaryItem xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema">
  <Data>
    <WordData>
      <Key>Hello</Key>
      <Meaning>Xin chào</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  hello
		  exclamation, noun
		  UK  /heˈləʊ/ US  /heˈloʊ/
		  (also mainly UK hallo); (hullo)

		  A1
		  used when meeting or greeting someone:
		  Hello, Paul. I haven't seen you for ages.
		  I know her vaguely - we've exchanged hellos a few times.
		  I just thought I'd call by and say hello.
		  And a big hello (= welcome) to all the parents who've come to see the show.
		  Từ mang ý nghĩa chào hỏi. Có thể dùng mỗi khi gặp một ai đó.</Explaination>
    </WordData>
 
    <WordData>
      <Key>Program</Key>
      <Meaning>Chương trình</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  a series of instructions that can be put into a computer in order to make it perform an operation:
		  a computer program
		  She's written a program to find words that frequently occur together.
		  Một tập hợp những câu lệnh được nạp vào máy tính để thực thi một tác vụ cụ thể</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>Computer</Key>
      <Meaning>Máy tính</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  an electronic machine that is used for storing, organizing, and finding words, numbers, and pictures, for doing calculations, and for controlling other machines:
		  a personal/home computer
		  All our customer orders are handled by computer.
		  We've put all our records on computer.
		  computer software/hardware
		  computer graphics
		  a computer program
		  Thiết bị hay hệ thống thực hiện tự động các phép toán số học dưới dạng số hoặc phép toán logic</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>Student</Key>
      <Meaning>Học sinh, sinh viên</Meaning>
      <Explaination>Những người đang được đi học tại các trường tiểu học, THCS, THPT hoặc các cơ sở giáo dục đại học, cao đẳng(sinh viên)</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>abbreviated</Key>
      <Meaning>Viết tắt</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  shorter than usual or shorter than expected:
		  They exchanged a passionate, but abbreviated, kiss.
		  The students were given an abbreviated intelligence test.
		  Cách viết ngắn gọn</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>absence</Key>
      <Meaning>vắng mặt</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
	he fact of not being where you are usually expected to be:
A new manager was appointed during/in her absence.
She has had repeated absences from work this year.
 Thêm các ví dụ
The smell of cigarette smoke confirmed what he had suspected: there had been a party in his absence.
I'm deputizing for the director during his absence.
Unbeknown to me, he'd gone and rented out the apartment in my absence.
Can you account for your absence last Friday?
A new manager was appointed during/in her absence.	  
	Không thể xuất hiện tại một nơi nào đó</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>accomplish</Key>
      <Meaning>Đạt được</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		 to finish something successfully or to achieve something:
The students accomplished the task in less than ten minutes.
She accomplished such a lot during her visit.
I feel as if I've accomplished nothing since I left my job. 
	  Có 1 thành tựu nào đó</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>admire</Key>
      <Meaning>Ngưỡng mộ</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		to find someone or something attractive and pleasant to look at:
We stood for a few moments, admiring the view.
I was just admiring your jacket, Delia.  
	  Thể hiện sự trầm trồ với một ai đó</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>adoration</Key>
      <Meaning>Yêu mến</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  very strong love or worship for someone:
her complete adoration of her brother
The painting depicts the Three Wise Men kneeling in adoration of the baby Jesus.
	  Có tình cảm đặc biệt với một ai đó</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>advocate</Key>
      <Meaning>Biện hộ</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		to publicly support or suggest an idea, development, or way of doing something:
[ + -ing verb ] She advocates taking a more long-term view.
He advocates the return of capital punishment.  
	  Cố tình bào chữa cho việc mình làm sai</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>affiliate</Key>
      <Meaning>liên kết</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  to cause a group to become part of or form a close relationship with another, usually larger, group, or organization:
a college affiliated to the University of Mumbai
The school is affiliated with a national association of driving schools.
	  Có một sự kết nối giữa các vật thể</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>aggressive</Key>
      <Meaning>Xâm lược</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  behaving in an angry and violent way towards another person:
The stereotype is that men tend to be more aggressive than women.
If I criticize him, he gets aggressive and starts shouting.
	  Chiếm một cách trái phép của ai đó cái gì đó</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>aim</Key>
      <Meaning>mục đích</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		 a result that your plans or actions are intended to achieve:
My main aim in life is to be a good husband and father.
Our short-term aim is to deal with our current financial difficulties, but our long-term aim is to improve the company's profitability.
The leaflet has been produced with the aim of increasing public awareness of the disease. 
	  Một điều hướng tới của bản thân trong tương lai</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>alias</Key>
      <Meaning>Bí danh</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  used when giving the name that a person is generally known by, after giving their real name:
	  Tên gọi bí mật hoặc ít người biết</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>ambiguous</Key>
      <Meaning>mơ hồ</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  having or expressing more than one possible meaning, sometimes intentionally:
His reply to my question was somewhat ambiguous.
The wording of the agreement is ambiguous.
The government has been ambiguous on this issue.
	    Một trạng thái mông lung không rõ ràng</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>analogy</Key>
      <Meaning>sự giống nhau</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		a comparison between things that have similar features, often used to help explain a principle or idea:
He drew an analogy between the brain and a vast computer.
It is sometimes easier to illustrate an abstract concept by analogy with (= by comparing it with) something concrete.  
	  Không có sự khác biệt</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>angel</Key>
      <Meaning>Thiên thần</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  a spiritual being in some religions who is believed to be a messenger of God, usually represented as having a human form with wings:
According to the Bible, an angel told Mary that she would have God's son, Jesus.
 
someone who is very good, helpful, or kind:
Be an angel and help me with this.
	Thường ngự trị trên thiên đường</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>antidote</Key>
      <Meaning>
		 a chemical, especially a drug, that limits the effects of a poison:
Sales of nerve gas antidotes increased dramatically before the war.
 
a way of preventing or acting against something bad:
Regular exercise is the best antidote to tiredness and depression. 
	thuốc độc</Meaning>
      <Explaination>Một loại thuốc có thể gây chết người</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>append</Key>
      <Meaning>nối thêm</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		to add something to the end of a piece of writing:
The author appends a short footnote to the text explaining the point.  
	kéo dài, thêm vào một cái gì đó</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>approach</Key>
      <Meaning>tiếp cận</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  to come near or nearer to something or someone in space, time, quality, or amount:
We could just see the train approaching in the distance.
If you look out of the window on the left, you'll see that we're now approaching the Eiffel Tower.
I see it's approaching lunchtime, so let's take a break.
In my opinion, no other composers even begin to approach (= come near in quality to) Mozart.
The total amount raised so far is approaching (= almost) $1,000.
He's very active for a man approaching 80 (= who is almost 80 years old).
	  Đến gần một sự vật nào đó</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>argument</Key>
      <Meaning>tranh luận</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		a disagreement, or the process of disagreeing:
The children had an argument about/over what game to play.
He got into an argument with Jeff in the pub last night.
A decision was finally made after some heated argument.  
	  Trình bày và bảo vệ những quan điểm khác nhau về một vấn đề gì đó</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>art</Key>
      <Meaning>nghệ thuật</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		the making of objects, images, music, etc. that are beautiful or that express feelings:
Can television and pop music really be considered art?
I enjoyed the ballet, but it wasn't really great art.  
	  Từ dùng chung cho âm nhạc, điện ảnh, hội họa,..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>aware</Key>
      <Meaning>nhận biết</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		 knowing that something exists, or having knowledge or experience of a particular thing:
[ + that ] I wasn't even aware that he was ill.
Were you aware of the risks at the time?
She was well (= very) aware that he was married.
"Has Claude paid the phone bill?" "Not as far as I'm aware." (= I don't think so)
I suddenly became aware of (= started to notice) him looking at me. 
	  Có ý thức về một điều gì đó</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>backbone</Key>
      <Meaning>xương sống</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
	the line of bones down the centre of the back that provides support for the body:
She stood with her backbone rigid.	  
	Là xương quan trọng nhất cơ thể, chạy dọc theo lưng</Explaination>
    </WordData>
  </Data>
  <WordData>
      <Key>bandwidth</Key>
      <Meaning>băng thông</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  a measurement of the amount of information that can be sent between computers, through a phone line, etc.:
The system will handle signals that need high bandwidth, for instance those that encode TV pictures.
high-bandwidth services/applications
	Lưu lượng dữ liệu truyền tải trong mạng</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>barely</Key>
      <Meaning>vừa đủ</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
	by the smallest amount:
They have barely enough (= no more than what is needed) to pay the rent this month.
She was barely (= only just) 15 when she won her first championship.	  
	Một trạng thái không thừa không thiếu</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>blessing</Key>
      <Meaning>phước lành</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
	a request by a priest for God to take care of a particular person or a group of people, or God's act of doing this:
The mass always ends with a blessing.
We ask God's blessing on Joan at this difficult time.	  
	Những điều an lành chúng ta thường cầu nguyện</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>breath</Key>
      <Meaning>hơi thở</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
	the air that goes into and out of your lungs:
Her breath smelled of garlic.
She was dizzy and short of breath (= unable to breathe in enough air).
He burst into the room, red-faced and out of breath (= unable to breathe comfortably because of tiredness or excitement).	  
	Sự hô hấp của con người</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>Chalk</Key>
      <Meaning>Phấn</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
	a type of soft white rock	  
	Dụng cụ để viết lên bảng sử dụng trong giảng dạy và học tập</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>claw</Key>
      <Meaning>Móng vuốt</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  one of the sharp curved nails at the end of each of the toes of some animals and birds:
Our cat likes to sharpen her claws on the legs of the dining table.
	Vật sắt nhọn có ở chân ở một số loài động vật</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>collaboration</Key>
      <Meaning>Sự hợp tác</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		the situation of two or more people working together to create or achieve the same thing:
The two playwrights worked in close collaboration (with each other) on the script.
The new airport is a collaboration between two of the best architects in the country.  
	Nhiều người cũng làm chung một việc gì đó</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>collide</Key>
      <Meaning>va chạm </Meaning>
      <Explaination>
	(especially of moving objects) to hit something violently:
The two vans collided at the crossroads.
It was predicted that a comet would collide with one of the planets.	  
	sự tác động lực vào nhau của hai hay nhiều vật</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>colonize</Key>
      <Meaning>thuộc địa hóa</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
	to send people to live in and govern another country:
Peru was colonized by the Spanish in the 16th century.	  
	chiếm đất, đàn áp người dân ở 1 vùng nào đó</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>commit</Key>
      <Meaning>cam kết</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		to do something illegal or something that is considered wrong:
He was sent to prison for a crime that he didn't commit.
to commit adultery/murder
to commit an offence  
	thực hiện một giao kèo với ai đó</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>companion</Key>
      <Meaning>Đồng hành </Meaning>
      <Explaination>
	a person you spend a lot of time with often because you are friends or because you are travelling together:
The dog has been her constant companion these past ten years.
a travelling companion	  
	Cùng thực hiện một điều gì đó với người khác</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>complexion</Key>
      <Meaning>nước da</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
	the natural appearance of the skin on a person's face, especially its colour or quality:
a dark/fair complexion
a healthy/clear/spotty complexion	  
	Màu sắc trên da</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>component</Key>
      <Meaning>thành phần </Meaning>
      <Explaination>
	a part that combines with other parts to form something bigger:
television/aircraft/computer components
The factory supplies electrical components for cars.
The course has four main components: business law, finance, computing and management skills.
Fresh fruit and vegetables are an essential component of a healthy diet.
The control of inflation is a key component of the government's economic policy.	  
	Bộ phận, chi tiết của một vật nào đó</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>comprehend</Key>
      <Meaning>hiểu</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
	to understand something completely:
I fail to comprehend their attitude.
He doesn't seem to comprehend the scale of the problem
[ + question word ] I'll never comprehend why she did what she did.
[ + that ] I don't think he fully comprehends that she won't be here to help him.	  
	rõ ràng trong suy nghĩ về một điều gì đó</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>comprehendsive</Key>
      <Meaning>toàn diện </Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  complete and including everything that is necessary:
We offer you a comprehensive training in all aspects of the business.
Is this list comprehensive or are there some names missing?
He has written a fully comprehensive guide to Rome.
		  đa năng, không bị thiếu sót một mảng nào</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>windpipe</Key>
      <Meaning>khí quản</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
	the tube in the body that carries air that has been breathed in from the upper end of the throat to the lungs:
She coughed and choked when a piece of food went down her windpipe.	  
	bộ phận nằm ở cổ, hỗ trợ hô hấp cho cơ phể người</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>window</Key>
      <Meaning>cửa sổ</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  a space usually filled with glass in the wall of a building or in a vehicle, to allow light and air in and to allow people inside the building to see out:
Is it all right if I open/close the window?
He caught me staring out of the window.
I saw a child's face at the window.
She has some wonderful plants in the window (= on a surface at the bottom of the window).
I was admiring the cathedral's stained-glass windows.
Have you paid the window cleaner (= person whose job is to clean the outside of windows)?
window frames
	cửa nhỏ, lấy gió và ánh sáng cho nhà</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>wheel</Key>
      <Meaning>bánh xe</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		a circular object connected at the centre to a bar, used for making vehicles or parts of machines move:
I got my bag caught in the wheel of my bicycle.
He lost control of his car when a front/rear wheel hit a rock as he approached the first bend.  
	các bánh xe giúp xe di chuyển trên mặt đường</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>vulnerable</Key>
      <Meaning>dễ bị tổn thương</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  able to be easily physically, emotionally, or mentally hurt, influenced, or attacked:
I felt very vulnerable, standing there without any clothes on.
It is on economic policy that the government is most vulnerable.
Tourists are more vulnerable to attack, because they do not know which areas of the city to avoid.
	  </Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>Vibrate</Key>
      <Meaning>rung</Meaning>
      <Explaination>
		  to shake slightly and quickly, or to cause something to do this, in a way that is felt rather than seen or heard:
The whole station seemed to vibrate as the express train rushed through.
His voice vibrated with anger.
	  </Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>unusual</Key>
      <Meaning>bất thường</Meaning>
      <Explaination>Không bình thường</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>unintended</Key>
      <Meaning>Ngoài ý muốn</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>trigger</Key>
      <Meaning>Kích hoạt</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>Transmission</Key>
      <Meaning>Truyền</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>trait</Key>
      <Meaning>đặc điểm</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>tractor</Key>
      <Meaning>máy kéo</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>toss</Key>
      <Meaning>quăng</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>synchronize</Key>
      <Meaning>đồng bộ</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>symestry</Key>
      <Meaning>đối xứng</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>sweat</Key>
      <Meaning>mồ hôi</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>summer</Key>
      <Meaning>mùa hè</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>summary</Key>
      <Meaning>tóm lược</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>suffocate</Key>
      <Meaning>chết ngạt</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>suffer</Key>
      <Meaning>đau khổ</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>subversion</Key>
      <Meaning>lật đồ</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>subset</Key>
      <Meaning>tập con</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>stuff</Key>
      <Meaning>đồ đạc</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>stubborn</Key>
      <Meaning>bướng bỉnh</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>strategy</Key>
      <Meaning>chiến lược </Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>sterible</Key>
      <Meaning>khử trùng</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>spit</Key>
      <Meaning>khạc nhổ</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>spectacualarly</Key>
      <Meaning>ngoạn mục</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>sparingly</Key>
      <Meaning>tiết kiệm</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>sow</Key>
      <Meaning>gieo</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>sincerity</Key>
      <Meaning>sự chân thành</Meaning>
      <Explaination></Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>shelter</Key>
      <Meaning>nơi trú ẩn</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>section</Key>
      <Meaning>phần</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>screw</Key>
      <Meaning>đinh ốc</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>scratch</Key>
      <Meaning>vết trầy</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>schema</Key>
      <Meaning>lược đồ</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>scar</Key>
      <Meaning>vết sẹo </Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>scalable</Key>
      <Meaning>có thể mở rộng</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>rust</Key>
      <Meaning>rỉ sét</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>restraint</Key>
      <Meaning>kiềm chế</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>repository</Key>
      <Meaning>kho</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>reponsible</Key>
      <Meaning>chịu trách nhiệm</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>report</Key>
      <Meaning>báo cáo</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>reminded</Key>
      <Meaning>nhắc nhở</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>refuse</Key>
      <Meaning>từ chối</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>reflection</Key>
      <Meaning>sự phản chiếu</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>refactoring</Key>
      <Meaning>tái cấu trúc</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>reduntdant</Key>
      <Meaning>dư thừa</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>rebase</Key>
      <Meaning>phục hồi</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>ratio</Key>
      <Meaning>tỉ lệ</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>radical</Key>
      <Meaning>căn bản</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>quantity</Key>
      <Meaning>định lượng</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>quality</Key>
      <Meaning>chất lượng</Meaning>
      <Explaination></Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>pursue</Key>
      <Meaning>theo đuổi</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>purpose</Key>
      <Meaning>mục đích</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>disturb</Key>
      <Meaning>làm phiền</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>distinguish</Key>
      <Meaning>phân biệt</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
	<WordData>
		<Key>discription</Key>
		<Meaning>mô tả</Meaning>
		<Explaination>..</Explaination>
	</WordData>
	<WordData>
		<Key>conjunction</Key>
		<Meaning>..</Meaning>
		<Explaination>..</Explaination>
	</WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>dispose</Key>
      <Meaning>vứt bỏ</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>diagram</Key>
      <Meaning>biểu đồ</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>devotion</Key>
      <Meaning>sự tận tâm</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>devoted</Key>
      <Meaning>hết lòng</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>despair</Key>
      <Meaning>tuyệt vọng</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>ease</Key>
      <Meaning>giảm bớt</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>entire</Key>
      <Meaning>toàn bộ</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
    <WordData>
      <Key>entity</Key>
      <Meaning>thực thể</Meaning>
      <Explaination>..</Explaination>
    </WordData>
</DictionaryItem>